All right. So, today we're going to
cover installing Visual Studio Code on a
Mac. So, open up a web browser and type
download Visual Studio Code and then
search.
And it's going to be the top result
here. So, I'm going to click on that.
Here you can see there's an option to
download Visual Studio for Windows or
for a Mac. We are going to go with the
Mac since we're on a Mac today. Takes a
second for the zip file to download.
Once that's downloaded, I'm going to
check on it real quick. And it looks
like we're close to done. All right,
we're done. Okay, so I'm going to open
it up from the bottom panel in
downloads. Open up that zip folder. That
unzips the file. And now we have Visual
Studio Code. I'm going to drag it into
applications.
Now we can see that we've got Visual
Studio Code in our applications.
So, we're gonna take that and I'm also
going to attach it to the launch bar at
the bottom just for ease of access.
Once I've done that, I'm going to go
ahead and double click on that. And that
will open up uh Visual Studio Code. It
asks if you trust this app since you've
downloaded it from the internet. We do.
And so, once you see this screen, it
means you've successfully installed
Visual Studio Code and you are safe to
move on with the rest of the course.